{
    "id": "eefacf13b87a404e8f754766419df710",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is not …………………… intelligent as his brother.",
            "description": "Positive adjectives are used in the structure as...as...",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mt. Everest is the ………………………… peak in the world.",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare something with the whole group it belongs to. ",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "higher",
                "highest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Oranges are …………………….. than apples.",
            "description": "Cheaper is the comparative form of cheap. The comparative form is used before than. ",
            "answers": [
                "cheaper",
                "cheap",
                "more cheap"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t earn as …………………….. as you do.",
            "description": "Much is used to express uncountable ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "No other animal is …………………………. large as the blue whale.",
            "description": "Either as or so is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "more",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The pen is ………………………. than the sword.",
            "description": "Mightier is the comparative form of mighty. ",
            "answers": [
                "more mighty",
                "mightier",
                "more mightier"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Africa is ……………………….. than any other continent.",
            "description": "Use the comparative form before than.",
            "answers": [
                "more hot",
                "hotter",
                "as hot"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Beethoven is one of the ………………………….. composers of music.",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare one person with the whole group they belong to. ",
            "answers": [
                "great",
                "greatest",
                "greater"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Kashmir is …………………………. than any other place in India.",
            "description": "More beautiful is the comparative form of beautiful. ",
            "answers": [
                "beautiful",
                "more beautiful",
                "beautifuller"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Ravi is the …………………………. of my sons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "young",
                "younger",
                "youngest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Cancer is ………………………. than any other disease.",
            "description": "Deadlier is the comparative form of deadly. ",
            "answers": [
                "deadlier",
                "more deadly",
                "most deadly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You eat a lot ……………………… than I do.",
            "description": "More is the comparative form of much and many. ",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}